Balto: Wolf Quest is a family, animation, adventure
film directed by Phil Weinstein.
Balto and his daughter Aleu embark on a journey of adventure and self discovery.
Balto (voice), played by Maurice LaMarche.
Jenna (voice), played by Jodi Benson.
Aleu (voice), played by Lacey Chabert.
Nava the Wolf Shaman (voice), played by David Carradine.
Niju the Evil Wolf (voice), played by Mark Hamill.
Boris (voice), played by Charles Fleischer.
Balto II: Wolf Quest is a 2002 American direct-to-video animated
adventure film produced and directed by Phil Weinstein.
It is the sequel to Universal Pictures/Amblin
Entertainment's 1995 Northern animated film Balto.
The film explores themes of cartoon, cartoon wolf, cartoon animal.